Thank you for watching!
Kettle and Idol
And second, the number of letters.
Yes, people say I have a lot of letters
when you're talking.
I mean, when you're talking, the number of letters means you're talking long.
No, it's not long.
I talk fast.
That's why I'm so tight.
It's a lot of words, but it's a lot of words.
Well, when I transcribed it after all.
I probably said twice as much as most people.
What do you mean?
What about your blog or your Instagram?
I'm not so sure about Instagram.
I try to keep it short.
I try to keep it short, but there's a character limit on Twitter too.
I get a "beep, beep, beep" from people.
That's a long time.
It's sometimes broken up into several pieces.
Yes, but I try to keep it all in one.
I'm trying to cram as much as I can into one.
Like the greeting at the end of the show and the closing speech.
The five of us have to say different things to each other.
I don't want to say anything out of the ordinary.
I have to say a lot of things without thinking about it.
So these speeches tend to be long.
Yes, it does take a long time.
In what order do you always come first?
I'm third, in the middle...
Oh, I see. You're in the center.
By position.
Well, I'm in order of age.
Is that in order of age?
Yes, from the audience's point of view.
From left to right, probably in order of age.
The middle one is longer. That's not so bad.
You don't think that's enough?
No, no, I don't think so.
But you draw your own pictures.
But since you draw your own pictures, people sometimes tell you that.
Yes, I get that a lot.
They say you're a star painter.
A star prostitute?
No, I don't think so.
But if you transcribe what I've been saying...
I think it's longer than other idols who appear at night.
It's probably longer than some of the other nighttime idols.
Longer?
Yes, it is.
Do the members tell you that?
No, but I think they're used to it.
You might not feel it too much.
That's right. It just happens to be that long.
I don't think it's going to be long.
It feels like it's packed.
If it's packed with a lot of words...
You're a fast talker?
Yes, he talks very fast.
That's true. Listen to me.
I'm told to speak slowly.
Is that so?
Is that what you do back home?
Well, yes... basically, this is how I do it.
Basically, like this.
Do you have any siblings?
I have a younger sister. She probably speaks more slowly.
Your sister speaks more slowly than you. My sister speaks faster and uses more letters.
Yes, but maybe more than most people.
Does that mean you're family?
I don't know.
What about your mother and father?
Oh, but... well, I think the environment I live in is normal.
I see.
I don't understand. Are there many?
Does that mean there are a lot of letters in your family?
I have a feeling so.
But, you mean you feel the same way as an egg, right?
Yes, the amount of words we speak and other things don't change much.
It's genetic.
Yes, it's genetic.
It was genetic, wasn't it?
Well, yes, but...
Secondly, you mentioned the number of words.
When you deliver a message, you don't say, "Oh my God, I'm so excited!
It's like, "Wow, this is fun!
This show is...
Mr. Katsu
Momo Gummi Popper
Mr. Yoppa and Mr. Pachi
Mr. Nickname Shisan
Mr. Goo Goo Dan Hirora
We sent this article courtesy of the following people!
Thank you very much for your contribution!
Please check back next time!
Bye-bye!